Yes, hello, hello.
I threw away the old microphone arm and
if it keeps talking without any details, I'll
switch back to the earphones I was using before. Please tell me. I
played around with the settings a little bit, but is it
still weird? Is it still crackling?
Please tell me the items.
And the small sound
keeps
coming from here? Oh, this is light. I'll ask again. 4 2 4. Another day, opinions differ, but isn't it? I'll just turn the volume up a little more.
Now,
this, this, every time it dries, it keeps talking more. When I
listened to it again, it was like that. Wait
a minute. Should
I just
use earphones? So, ultimately, we need to see which has better sound quality.
If earphones come out more, it's better to use the air conditioner.
How about earphones, microphone,
etc.? Oh,
yes, I should
use earphones. What should I do? How is
the sound now? I don't
know much about this,
but it seemed weird, so I touched it.
Oh, I'll
put it at about 4 and
see.
Yes, the
earphones are the same today. Like this. Do you have
another microphone?
Open. I remember it coming bundled with the phone when I bought it.
I guess I'll just have to do what I have. I'll go through it. Should I buy a bike? I can't forget that I'm in such a good environment. This tube cam w Today, I uploaded that video today, what was it? Yes,
it's just the surface.
Inside, anyway, like this, last time I talked about hair loss, what should I talk about this time, and
people asked me to talk about hormones, so I couldn't. This hair loss
story was quite long back then, and the local strike center
was like, what, 30 minutes? But now, the hormone story,
hair loss, vitamin B7, and things like that
don't need to be long, so I thought it would be too much, so I'll split it up a bit. I was a little lazy, and I
didn't have enough time to prepare. So, I prepared the
most basic thyroid hormone.
So, like number 2, I
heard a brief story about the price increase and left. The deputy
manager. Um, here's the first basic content.
Yes, you can see it. Then, you can see
it, right? I
'll write it so that it's not visible. I
tried to prepare a picture of the thyroid, but there was
n't a good time to get the thyroid written down.
Because of volume 6, of course, that weird thing, and then I said, "I don't know the conditions well," and just did it.  Please
do it moderately.
Oh,
then the
thyroid gland.
Also, let's make it from 6 o'clock. We're going to
hurry up and put in just one color for Priya.
Please. Today, we're going to organize the basics of the thyroid gland.
What does thyroid hormone formation do? This time, we're going to look at the basics.
Here's a picture. A person has a head and extends out to the body.
For example, the thyroid gland gives a command to make thyroid hormones and
secretes thyroid hormones like this from the thyroid gland in Geochang. You can
see the detailed process on the next slide. If you
look here, the
hormone is a negotiation hormone. It means that the three and the
keeper come out and do what they do. I briefly
wrote it down in English.
If you look at the ink list data, it's detailed. It increases metabolism in our body.
And then here, the centimeter text over 4. This
affects growth and development. Growth and development. Next, the ink race. The
catecholamine effect, which I mentioned earlier, is what catecholamines are talking about today.
Dopamine and epinephrine.  Compared to the song, let's take a look at the three hormones of cringe.
Just by listening to that, you can get a rough idea of ​​what they do in our bodies. Also,
epinephrine,
commonly known as adrenaline, is a problem.
Dopamine is more like that, and it's something that makes you excited. So, if we unpack these a little
more and
look at the role of thyroid hormones, you can
think of it as regulating homeostasis in the body.
Then, of course, there's heart rate, and
there's also laxity and tae-woong.
Heart rate, blood pressure, body temperature, all of these are affected by the second love, and then the second love hormone, lamin. When the
heart rate increases and becomes stronger, blood
pressure rises, and when metabolism increases, body temperature also rises.
2. It's a
catabolic effect. From our third perspective, this means catabolic action. It's a little hot now.
To put it simply, it increases our body's
metabolism and glycogen, which is fatty acid oxidation.
This means that glycogen, which is stored in our body, becomes fuel. It's carbohydrates. It's
glucose that accumulates in our body, like photo.  Let's look at body fat.
So,
if our thyroid function is hyperactive, this room also burns vigorously, and the
body's metabolism is too good, so if we
eat like this, we
lose weight in an instant and the standard continues to decrease.
But now, on the other hand, if our thyroid function is low,
these fat-related conditions don't work, so we gain a lot of weight and hold on to
more fat.
This is because
thyroid hormones are shot, but... oh, hello, this is related.
This is gray, meaning it's involved with the body.
Ultimately, they're connected. This room is more involved in peristalsis, so
if the leak thyroid is a symbol of each other,
peristalsis works too well, so we have to
go to the bathroom three times a day, five times a day, and so on.
Conversely, if the symbiotic function is low,
constipation occurs. If peristalsis is not working and the thyroid gland is low, constipation
doesn't just occur. Our body's stomach acid doesn't produce enough, and these pediatric elements don't produce enough, so
various problems arise. We'll look into this more later, but if the stomach acid
doesn't produce enough, it doesn't work.
Well,
basically, food digestion is poor, and poor digestion
means that it's not working well, so it
makes the problem worse. Then, it's
involved in the secretion of thyroid hormones, and it's involved in the secretion of insulin, and
when the thyroid hormone becomes high, Lee Soon-im's sincerity is created, and Min-sik's
sensitivity to intimacy decreases,
so now, as a result, you gain more weight and
hold on to more parts, and that's what we're talking about.
I'm preparing a picture of the bee, and
there are people who think, "I hope this is thyroid function 2 for you." Even if you
don't have hypothyroidism,
if you eat Park Sang-seon's thyroid, wouldn't it be better to lose weight and improve in other ways?
As I said before, our body regulates homeostasis, and awakening and
improvement have to be very tightly regulated. It's a
very narrow window. I
don't know how to say it in Korean, but it
has to be regulated within a narrow window. Yes, it's regulated within a narrow inner.
Yes, it's
always going back and forth. This person is a symbol, but it's not good, and
of course, it became me and  It's not good, but the reason why is that
? If you look at the star chart, you'll know what it is because of the 2 Hongseong videos. They don't even look like they're flying.
If you think about it, these guys have hyperactive 2 ferry park ascent functions. Their
thyroid is hyperactive, so they flap their wings once per second,
and their
intestines beat incredibly fast. These guys save
4 years and
die young.
Everything happens too quickly, they live quickly and
die quickly. So if you think about it the other way around, it's a bit
slothful.
Turtles are especially like that. Turtles live next to turtles, right? You
can think of it that way.
Of course, that doesn't mean that being slow is good this year.
It means that homeostasis must be well maintained. I'll
take a closer look at the process of thyroid hormone secretion.
Ah, if you look here, it's called hyper color must. It's a
very old period within the hypothalamus, and it's a little bit.
Inside it is this part, and this hypothalamus is very
Let's
quickly report to the second period, the upper and lower levels. Yes,
the book TTA Clank. And here is Park Sang-seon, who is when we come to the neck. If we
compare this whole thing, the
upper and lower levels are the manager, and the
most and Eri. If we think about it as hormones, it's done. When
our body needs thyroid hormone, the
manager gives instructions. He tells the most to
do this. He has to secrete something called PRH. This is a
trucking release hormone called thyroid-stimulating hormone-releasing hormone.
It tells Eri to release thyroid-stimulating hormone. Hey, you guys have to do the schedule, so this
manager is telling
Eri to do it again.
ESH. You've all heard of this at least once. It's
called thyroid-stimulating hormone. When the
hormone that stimulates the thyroid is secreted from the lower body, the
dean receives two orders and
kisses Lee and Leaf thyroid hormones. The thyroid hormones that are actually used are
prepared like this.
And like this, T3.  When the keeper is secreted, the kiss-ling keeper
circulates through the bloodstream like this, and
feedback is written to the upper and lower Rum Vegas bodies, and a signal is sent, so we are now
producing enough. 1.
So, if we tell it to stop and not to add more, it will
understand 4 and stop producing unnecessary tra, TF, and LH.
So, our body is maintaining homeostasis.
But if you look here, the pastry and keeper are blocked like this.
In fact, it's like this. Does it go like this? It does
n't just come out like this even if T3 wants to come back. In fact, it looks like this. When
the thyroid is stimulated by KSH, it
doesn't produce the same kill-su tempo as the hormone stimulated, but it produces an overwhelming amount of T-pulse.
Catherine only makes permission and releases it.
Why is that?
Number 6 is this activated state.
Number 6 is a countermeasure in our body, but it doesn't actually do battle.
And while doing that, it
performs the role of the thyroid hormone that I mentioned earlier in the body that actually works.  Hormones are what
actually do this kissing human story, and the
keeper is inactive. Our bodies secrete this keeper when we sleep, and
in the blood urine that comes, it exists for a long time, and Eunchan slowly converts the inside of the car
into Tistory.
If we receive this TSH from our body and make T3 not too much, it
seems that the thyroid function 2nd act has become extremely hyperactive, so it is
easier to maintain the positivity and control it.
With the keeper made inside, the sound of rain is used as the keeper is converted little by little.
This change also occurs in the throat. Matcha O3 pods are actually used. The
conversion takes place in those small cells all over our body, and it
's gaming. But
yes, there are cases where it doesn't work. The
keeper should be converted into history, but
this conversion doesn't happen.
Other than that, if the conversion doesn't happen or if it
doesn't happen for some reason, there will be a next slide.
Anyway, if this camper doesn't convert into story, it doesn't just stay as a keeper
and wait for it to convert someday.
2  It's comfortable with a new hormone called reverse T3.
This Bursty Three is also activated despite being converted into a piece of cake.
Originally, it would normally be T3, increasing metabolism in our body and
doing the work that thyroid hormones should do. But it's become
inactive and turned into water.
But reverse T3 doesn't just stop there. This
Kiss Lee has many 8
kids who have to work with it. The cells that
have their own value bring it. The two of us compete.
That's why the influence of this T3 has been reduced. I don't
understand what Three should be doing.
2.22. Artist l. Not repairing. Iriver Betty Fur. How does Key Sul and
Reverse City change? If
you look briefly, you can see here. There's a feeling fur, right? With the gift recipe, what's hey, Iodine
iodine. It's a hormone with four iodine molecules attached like this. I
do it alone. But
yes, the one on the left is it.  If the video
falls like this, it becomes T3, but if the
one on the right falls, it becomes Ripper Street. If you look here,
there's a coefficient that says "DI is inside the clothes," right?
This i5 Dyne Ace, Ethiopia No. 2 Dyne, will
use the expression "transfer." It's the process of removing iodine.
As I said earlier, there are four iodine molecules, and the
terms are removed one by one. By
removing 5D, it changes to the active state, and of course, it
becomes reverse T3. Now, this is like the rest of the cell, and as it
falls, it becomes tip, and so on.
So,
how can 2T per be comfortably converted to Tistory? If my conversion doesn't work and it
becomes reverse Tistory, I'll talk about Park Sang-seon's health in
general. If you
look here, I'll
borrow this English 1 and explain it one by one in Korean, limiting the steps.
4. First, normal hormone production and keeper changes affect the factors
behind it.
Ah, here, there are 3 testers of Haksan. It says to use Homemon.
This is the dining table.
Here, we dial in these factors that cover the secretion of sex hormones normally. After looking at nutrients, iodine,
thyrophosphate, and a type of amino acid metabolite called a citrus fruit,
lamid, zinc, selenium,
vitamin E, B2, B3, B6, C group, and other nutrients like mipi, these nutrients must
be evenly distributed in our body so that the
thyroid can make hormones into a system.
Then, when the Hitoba Room 7 is
turned into a story, the nutrient keeper that helps change to Tistory contains the necessary
nutrients, such as
selenium and iron. Lee Jong-yong 2 Nutrition Book is very
important.
This selenium is necessary for the process I mentioned earlier to
remove
iodine. Selenium is absolutely necessary to remove iodine.
Ah, then the next thing is
iron, Selim Pro Cell Essence t-test Diet Alto Mons.
These are nutrients that cells use to be sensitive to hormones and respond well to them.
Imagine, the nutrients that help my cells respond well include amines,
zinc,
and exercise. There is a little exercise.  It
has to be active.
Yes, it's natural for our body's metabolism to function well.
Slightly on the contrary,
there are women who prevent the proper secretion of money from the table. There is stress, acute infection, and
then there is rock salt. The body is infected with bacteria.
Whether it's a virus or a bacteria,
when there is trauma, a large wound is caused, and mental and physical
trauma occurs.
When exposed to radiation or taking a chemotherapy drug, then there is something important.
Fluorine. Brown fluorine. It's not just fluorine.
All the elements on the side that you feel
are there. Eyebrows. You know,
loneliness.
There's also Tucker, but I suddenly can't remember. Blue and
suffering. Goat. Ah, I almost forgot. There is
goat. There is goat, rock,
goat, fluoride. These three things that came in pretend to be iodine in the place where iodine should go
and take that place. To
put it simply, iodine should be here, but it's here.
Here's what I need,
but it has bromine, fluorine, chlorine, and
iodine.
Of course, this hormone won't work properly.
Yes, like
that diode, they interact negatively with each other, and they compete with each other to
do these things. So, we have to be very careful. I
had to suggest consuming chlorine and fluorine.
Envy,
like bread, will increase in volume. Then, there will be
pesticides that can become toxic, and then there will be heavy metals
like cadmium and lead. I'm curious. If
there are metals, thyroid function will drop significantly.
Not to mention anti-inflammatory drugs.
In addition, there are autoimmune diseases like cellulitis,
so touch function will drop.
Then, the keeper
won't be able to convert normally to the story, and the reverse T3 will change.
These factors can cause stress, including
LS and trauma.
Next, the most important thing, in a way, is to
give a low-calorie diet. If you're on a low-calorie diet, what is this? It's a natural
plant-based diet.
Hosseini, the time of the week.  Or maybe it's just what ordinary people do, like
drinking a lot of alcohol and eating sweet potatoes on a diet, celery juice cleanse, etc.
Regardless of the diet,
if you're low in calories, the
ascending function decreases, and with reverse Tistory,
Super, and reverse steel, there are more.
* The court doesn't always give us the result of hitting our lifespan.
Then, if the inflammatory response is severe in the spring, it grows like this reverse tree.
Similar to the infection earlier, the heavy metals
that I mentioned above are poured out, and then,
not like this, but if this kidney problem occurs, it's not, but if the heart
functions properly, it's also eaten within the borders of the river, and some
drugs.
There are a few more things besides.
For example, chronic diseases are natural. In
addition, if the first room is too low, there are many reverse tests. The
embankment has gone over, but 4. These things have one thing in common. When our spring
is in a state of space,
when something doesn't feel right, this reverse also changes a lot. For
example, in the brain,
in the election, in our body, it's adding fuel to the fire.  I don't want to get swollen,
that's why.
Right now, it's
not the time to be pumping up your metabolism and pumping up your heart rate or being active.
We need to take care of ourselves a little more recently,
slow down work and physical activity.
This is our body telling us that we need to recover. It's not about going out and playing around, it's about
recovering. That's why this
Styx Lee is going up. In
other words, if our bodies are healthy, the G2 story will come out more, and our bodies will
be more active and lively.
And if there's no flower right now and there's no spray for some reason,
this story will come out more. I
don't remember the name of the Blanc house, so I hate it.
Ah, crazy. It's the same as the reamer. It's the
competition between the alveoli and the combined cells.
But besides this, I
'll just talk about this much today, but besides this, there are things that
lower the function of the stealing organ.
There are some that are listed here, but nutritionally, it's a bit too much. I've
talked about nutrients that improve thyroid function, but
haven't I mentioned things that are bad for it? Let's talk a little more about those that aren't mentioned.
I'll do it. If you
look at it this way, should we make it a little worse?
Yes, it's a labor union. Laertes, Burberry, bu, 2 feet, yes, Park Sang-soon, various causes that reduce function, I
've organized it all at once by coming to work. If you
look below, Perth also
has 5 and 16 generations, so you can think of it as someone who has seen everything at once. Let's
look at the diet list. FS2. You can think of it as the parts that are affected by what we eat during the period.
Fortunately, there is FS Tire Terra's bio.
This is what it is. Excessive iodine. If
we deal with iodine deficiency, of course, iodine is necessary for the thyroid gland to produce roman, so iodine
deficiency can
cause serious problems with thyroid function. However, if there is
too much iodine, it is
not good for the rise. There is
a lot of it. So, let's leave it. This is why iodine is important. Loading is really important and it is an essential product, but especially in these days when we are exposed to a lot of things like fluoride, sora, chlorine, and rom, nodes are important, but there
are people who use yodeling dome excessively.
Keyna will be  Who is lucky enough to have 4?
These days, it's rare to see this kind of thing, but
in the past, our country also had a lot of problems with excessive load. Because our country,
Japan, and other Asian countries, well,
not all countries in the East were like that, but we just
drank a lot of Taesan water. We ate more produce than the poor. We
ate a lot of fish.
So, we make a lot of marshmallow soup and often boil fish and
eat seafood. So, we usually eat plenty of seafood.
Now, we have a tradition. We
boil seaweed soup for mothers who give birth. So, after giving birth, we boil seaweed soup.
Where is the body? It's a really good memory.
But in the past, during the Joseon Dynasty, we
couldn't eat seaweed often. So, that tradition was very good.  There may be no tradition, but on this day,
when you're pregnant or
have your fifth child, you need more iodine.
These days, you already eat a lot of it,
but if you boil seaweed soup and eat beer pong three times a day, you'll
get too much iodine. So, there's a saying that
Koreans shouldn't get scolded after giving birth to a third child.
Because of the urethra, that iodine is a very important nutrient,
but I
hope you don't forget that only mothers eat that much.
At that time, the conditions were generally good. Jens. This is where it starts in earnest.
Boltro Jane is a general term for things that lower the function of the twins, a
general term for toxins that lower the thyroid gland.
These things are contained in all kinds of foods. Let's
take a look at them one by one. No,
first, fat plays a role. If you look here,
here, and I couldn't find this. If you
look here, there are a lot of different stories. If you look at the former Oh Se-cheol
and the staff pad group, the
level of FT Rock poets was higher than other kids.
Those of you who have lowered sexual performance.  You have to eat a lot of it.
Puzzles are something you can do if you eat them, so let's put all that aside and
look at 4.
If you feed it oil, the
synthetic production is greatly reduced.
What is the oxidized energy? Of course, the
Ulsan oil, the seed oil, the B8, the oil in the Daebu Tini industry, if you
cook it once more and eat it terribly, of course, the F
box is not reduced, but you shouldn't eat that kind of thing.
Next, the role of green tea,
green tea, because you also eat green tea, something like this, to txt is reduced and TSH is increased, and then the
thyroid function is reduced to the target, so it spread.
Come here, soybean,
look here, here, here, this point, here, here, this is a simple summary.
Beans, reverse point, Jenny, where is it, followed by pound in quart, Jenny,
end, and only
then, this is sheep, molly, um, there is something like this, here, if you do
cabbage, cauliflower, broccoli, conspiracy, Pasa, look
at night, So Elso, eh pro. If you look here, this is soybean, soybean-made kina,
soybeans are terribly bad, so
two are one.  It's better to emphasize it more.
There are things like this, and here it comes out again.
This one is also made of Etro. Atoo is
not really a fight estrogen, but it's a high-strength Etrozen 2-kan. If you
eat it, especially people with a healthy thyroid, if you eat it, you have to take
thyroid hormone medication that lowers thyroid function. It's very dangerous.
Why is it now aro fun camp camp? Bye. My nickname is Kai Bye. Did
Eve say cyanide? You're
special. No matter what? Give me cyanide. Did you hear it correctly?
There are some that contain red cyanide in cyanide soup.
App Bulro. Now, it's not an amount that will kill you right away, but research results show that these
plant-based foods that have cyanide
contribute to lowering the twin-win function in our body.
In this experiment, you became blonde. * If it's
holly pea cabbage, uh, sonmu
5, boksun saba,
these things play a role in lowering the new function of the bag. If you
boil this and drink the water, that's the worst.
Since it comes out in water, and now the cooked things come out of the magpie cage and the
moisture content is reduced and the
concentrated things are hung, those things are the next
strongest and then the increase and the inclusion and the increase and the
p ring is the most representative
substance that plays a role in almost twisted sounds, and this is exactly what is in it.
Orta Baga Summer
SCX Here is the brass painter cross plant.
Broccoli cauliflower cabbage, etc. It is
said that it is okay to eat it cooked here, but it is not like this.
Low-priced chips and plants are in it, and retro sinners
originally do not contain it when the plants are alive.
If the plant itself contains such a strong reading, it is not good for the plant itself. It is
poison to the plant. It is
medicine to the plant and not to the monster. It is poison to the plant and to the 2
people.
So, since this can't be lived with all the time, the plants
put this in and store it. This is chemically soft matter. I said that it is the master of chemical warfare against plants.
Chemically, the
two blue cutscene oleic tra micro lines are isolated from each
other and stored like this. When this plant is
eaten, or if it bites itself,
or if a person comes and pulls it out, or if there is an external attack, these
two substances meet and combine,
turning into a toxin like a point ring.
So, but among these two,
1 glucose oleic and
6 slater meet.
Yes, a language fight.
Yes, clicker cellulite. Among these two, if you cook
one side,
it disappears. It becomes cold. If you cook it all, it seems to be greatly destroyed.
But the problem is that we also made this in our intestines.
This doesn't meet right away. You won't go to the reading right away, but our
intestines are taking this to our obstacle. Because this creates a type of obstacle, it
goes to that obstacle and combines like this, reacting and acting exactly the same.
Then, we have to get rid of it. Now, since we have an obstacle, the
way to get rid of it is through fermentation.
For example,
Titicaca.  Vegetables are the most representative food for us. We give them kimchi.
It's okay to eat it like that, but simply cooking it and
eating it is very,
very bad. Just cooking it and eating it
doesn't neutralize the toxins.
Moreover, grinding it raw and gulping it down like a detox juice without cooking it
prevents the thyroid gland from absorbing the dirt on our table. The
iodine disappears. If
there is no iodine in our thyroid, thyroid hormones will not be produced.
This is the role of the story. I can't think about it well anymore. Next,
ground peanuts. I showed you last time. Kumho Estrogen. There are a
lot of things like that. Hong Kong throws them. That estrogen comes in a lot.
There is a role as a point, and any millet is the same.
Selene mother and vitamin B12 x alkyl
stella
chloric acid. This is a pair, but it's Jack Yunje.
I don't know if this is available in Korea.
This election puts a lot of
effort into it, but it's the same as the first one. The stainless steel array is made of plastic, and
even if it's BPA-free, it's the same as the DPS tree, so it's
the same. Blasting is the same. It's meaningless. p p p p p
[music]
Cafe pierced. In fact, we don't have many joints. And
then there are parabens in sunscreens.
Now, things like 5 estrogens, estrogens,
what's still the case? Parabens, those in perfumes or air fresheners, or
lavender scents,
or flaxseeds, soybeans, and concentrated fighter
estrogens, all of which lower thyroid function. So now, heavy metals, as we mentioned earlier, are
a little more common.
And the cheeks are not surprising. Smoking doesn't do anything. There are
so many different things that play a role in lowering our sexual function. We
can't avoid all of these. Realistically, it's impossible to avoid them all. Our
reality is the
21st century, so now,
we can do our best to avoid them.  To avoid this, we
need to think about this to some extent in our heads.
Like My Place, we need to know that we shouldn't give this to you. When we can avoid it, we
can break it even if we have to come to Korea. If we don't
know that this is bad and just keep eating it indiscriminately,
these things
won't happen. 1. What do you mean by LED tubes? It just keeps piling up and piling up and piling up. So, it's important to prevent things from happening as much as possible within the scope of my control.
Ah, so up to this point, we've
looked at what kinds of effects normal hormone production has.
Finally,
when checking thyroid levels, when he goes to the hospital to check his thyroid levels,
should he see his mother when he gets tested? That's very important. Because
even in our country, which is wary of foreign countries, there
are still a lot of doctors who have art shops, these two hearts, and phones.
When internists learn about the quantity of wheels, they say you only need to know these two things. They
're still using things they learned decades ago.
But 2T Pearl to T3  There are so many people who can't properly switch, so I
really want to see Reaper Shinjiro. There are many people who are completely useless, and
with just these two things, there are
so many things we don't know.
When we do a compatibility test, there's always
hysteria, KT Story, and VT Ports H2 Bus Kiss Lee.
There are thyroid autoimmune antibodies.
So, we can test for Hashimoto's disease, where the thyroid gland attacks the autoimmune thyroid.
With those two, we need to test six things.
That's all we've seen for today.
Next time, we'll talk about the relationship between protective virtue
virtual
estrogen and the thyroid gland, and other stories.
I'll find something suitable and prepare. I'll end it here.
Ah, this is something like this. Every time I do it,
it's amazing. It's
amazing. Yes,
10:49. The
story about Ultra was a bit long. At first, I
thought it would be short, but it's really not that great.
Ah, this, ah,
ahead of that, I'm having a hard time.
Something suddenly happens. I'm thinking about writing subtitles. Ha, earlier, the
main content. What am I? Okay.
First, I'll attach it here and
attach a pickle. And then the video
scrap fashion.  Video description Turkey, I know,
I know,
Ark, it's a
lot more dangerous than losing, um,
nothing, but yes, it seems good to put on subtitles, but I don't know, but the
villain was harder than I thought,
ah, it took too long,
4,
Ah,
I'll proceed as I've, each one feels quickly, 4,
company, company, hometown, a lot, so I'll do it, and
when I have a bad sore throat,
Ark, players,
so
Alban's proclamation, this umchi, advised me to split it, and
split it, and listened to it, but it was good, so
when I split my vagina, 4kg, and did you like it? Did
you continue to eat a lot in the ? This is also when the pastor gives you a loan for the idea, but it's normal, but it
all comes off from the body, and
oxalic acid crystals come out on the skin,
and then it gets better, but the body
really expels it, so it gives you too much opportunity to expel Elo in urine and feces, so it's
done with the skin.
There's English, so
ah, vegetables were like that too. This must have been a symptom of a billion-dollar idea loan.
* 4th daughter movie When excreting oxalic acid from the body, ah, I'm talking about this, but you have to
do a lot here and there.  But
many people don't know how difficult it is to do oxalate cabbage and other things. What happens when you excrete it?
When you excrete 4 years of carpentry, it accumulates in our bodies,
right? It's all over the body.
Okay, if you do an autopsy after those people die, you'll
see crystals in the thyroid gland, like in a percentage of people. Shelly, who's one
of the people who's done the most research on Lagos ideology,
has a pattern. If you go to his Instagram and look, you'll see
several messengers sent by people. It
's not really a thyroid thing, but a normal crystal
protruding from the bottom like this. It's a
4-year-old creek hair that was trapped inside and then came out. It's
excreted from our bodies. It comes out to a weak spot in our body, and
the joints that were sore are duffy.
Then, when you suspect a frame fob, it pours out from the brain, so it
comes out a lot in places like the face. There's a lot of blood flow,
so things like the gums and things like that get worse, and it's
really difficult in many ways.
Then,
all the grains.  Crystal, as a candidate, really, yes, yes,
later, we'll
have an interview and talk about what kind of experiences we've had. It's not like we have to do it once when we talk about options.
Anyway, that's right. It's a difficult diet.
So, when you eat oxalate, you don't know, you just eat a lot and
laugh. It's cold, and you can't store it anymore. You
don't eat it until it's too cold. It goes up.
That's why the idea of ​​options is dangerous. It's even more difficult.
People, no matter how much you warn them, have harsh thoughts.
Hmm, it's okay, but there were no problems before. As
you mentioned, there's no financial status related to oxalate.
After quitting for four years, I
suffered and suffered. I've seen hell. It's
like an orchid. Should I
eat kelp or not? It's
good everywhere, but it's
usually good. Eating kelp and taking elixirs are generally good. There's
a lot of work there,
loads, and the influences are many.
But eating it in moderation
can be sick. Like in our country, if you put it in tomorrow and boil it, you
can do it. 4. It's not good to wrap it up.
3. The law is too low, so don't mess around with the graph. Right?
These days.  Even if the probability is too low, if you look at it, f,
so here we're talking about Chinatsu or evidence, women are 50 centimeters, 15%, that's
about it, and
men should be a little more, but in the case of women, they have to be careful,
so the probability of finding it is very low, and in a state of low thyroid function, they
can't get pregnant. They can't incense, so if they're
suddenly pregnant and there's a famine, they can't endure it, so they just
felt that it was stable to drink a bottle of liquor.
Of course, this is also slowly over a long period of time, so
in one spring, they reassured me, and my current condition is okay. I'm okay now. I've
tried mahjong, and
in an open state, while being healthy, I slowly lowered it little by little. It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay. It's going down like this, and
flowers are like, well, outlets, it shouldn't be like this, but it's
okay to some extent. It's
not like that, but if you just starve yourself and
do a Chicago low-calorie diet and do this, your body fat percentage will get hurt and you'll use it.
Genesis is all dropping, and it's all dropping from the spring, and you can't have strength, and it's going to increase
tremendously.
Note Nutrition 3 characters
There is no need to eat the large form of our country's island 4. You
can eat it in March. The
preferential nutritional supplement is that, and the
sea is called Irving, and there are no people who can receive it if you fly for 5 hours. The
people of the country do not need a board suit.
IPO Blon,
what is Nexon? They
eat bread with some in it three times a day, 365 days a year, and all the iodine in their bodies
is replaced with fromm. It may not be usable temporarily.
Even if it is not usable temporarily, it is
not good to eat it consistently. It varies slightly depending on the amount.
Doctor, ice is good for blood. Ugh, imagine what it is. Even if a lot comes out, we are
not using it properly while watching.
Usually, this has a slightly opposite effect in keto.
People who have been eating a planned diet for a long time and are healthy know the bow dog Kango who vomits quickly.
Ah, like this, 2, 4, like
this. The light is a bit weird, but
what can I do? What can I do? What is the hound tank?
Those who have been doing this well have a
hysteria level that drops, and TSH is with us.  Do you know? The
efficiency of T3 use has improved.
Just as our body's insulin sensitivity has improved, so has insulin efficiency.
Metabolic efficiency and T3 efficiency.
This is what we can see as ideal. If
there's the opposite, so that
the body can cool down a bit so that it can pull up the church well,
avoid apps that can lower thyroid function as much as possible, and also use
R13 and have good lifestyle habits. Digestion must be good, and it's
not something that can be changed simply by fixing one thing.
At that time, when dieting, yin and yang dechim aharu was largely monopolized.
Oh, yes, that's the side.
O Curly The Mind
Opera breakfast,
right?
Then spinach is good. * During the next 5.7 news, if you ate it every day, it's... Eun. Okay, if
you do that, it's obviously not good for your health.
Kimchi, Okso, and Sanim. If you choose the most, spinach is in it.
Omega 5 is accumulated, and * Sanim is a mineral drink.
So, you can get all the minerals.  You'll experience all the things that happened before, and because
you're metabolizing oxalic acid,
all the glutathione in your body is consumed, and it can't be diffused and it creates inflammation,
and what's with
mushrooms? Because the intestinal bacteria layer is all destroyed,
so it can't be considered safe.
Come on, each mushroom is really different. You
can't lump them all together and talk about them. To put it simply,
there are mushrooms, right?
Well, the poisonous mushrooms we're talking about here are the ones that cause
serious problems if you eat them, and they're called posasi. But the mushrooms that aren't like that, the
mushrooms that we eat, they're not all that poisonous and they're not all safe.
Come on, those things are
4 Greek, ah, Greek,
and things like that. If they reach that state, you just
give them to them and they're guaranteed, right?
Um.  Here's a mushroom that my son has
in his mouth. Yes, there are some good ones that are good for the time being, right? Those buttons, you guys,
those things are hilarious,
so you have to eat them when they burst. I know that many of them disappear. They've been destroyed, so you can eat them raw. And
of course, my English
dad said 3 4 1, did they come off?
Oh,
oh, it's just a chaga mushroom. Some of
them
definitely have a lot of salt in the West Mountain area, so the carriage saw them, so they wrote down a top spoonful of that on their waist and
informed us like this, and it can also be powdered.
Of course, there aren't many people who eat it five times a day. But
that's also now, and after knitting, among them, it's a familiar.
It's a great mask.
Um, the boss, the priest, Johnny
comes, and there are mushrooms, and there are
good mushrooms, and I received it.
Safety is the appearance, so
strictly speaking, it's not a newspaper, but now it's not new water, but 1. You might
have thought about why plants are so poisonous in the first place. Then, you
can't move your feet because you save them.  That's right.
If someone attacks you, you can't get out because your roots are embedded,
so now, just like mushrooms defend themselves with their bodies, mushrooms
aren't wells,
but they are molds. I think they have embedded roots, so
eat them while thinking about this. It's
not safe to walk, and you can consider everything light.
Cabbage curry, the head of the water, is very narrow.
Wouldn't it be good? Like you, from the back, all the way to the inside. Because of that, I studied well.
This card is a god.
Eat sheep. Oh, right.
I'm thinking of quitting walking for now. After quitting, I
hope you see if it doesn't look good. After that, I hope you take a good look. The reason why
digestion doesn't get better after giving birth is because
women use a lot of hormones after giving birth, so the
ascending function often gets worse.
We hid the rooftop a lot, so I don't know what the ascending function is like,
but I
wonder if the twin function is reduced and pediatrics isn't working well.
If that's the case, it would be good to resolve the cause of the thyroid gland now. It's
not that bad at all in the beginning of the flock. It's
really good.  Since there is no such thing as giving too much, if digestion is not good, no one will clean it up, so I think
it is a supplement, so I think it is like taking a supplement. In normal times, various chemical detergents, cosmetics, food, and necessary things like music, skin, respiratory organs, shampoo, cosmetics, detergents, perfume, woods, sympathy, and amalgams cannot be done. This is really true. 2
All of these are like this. No, you may ask how you can live by examining each and every one of these things, but
that is why you are not feeling well right now.
How can you live brightly with waste tires, children, and North Port? If
you live without avoiding everything, the process will end like this.
There are people who do not avoid such things and are healthy.
There are people who do not have problems and live very healthily. But those people are the ones who
cannot live like that. And this is the teacher.
This child is not healthy.
No, he has a thyroid. I don't know about the two progressively.
Through that, as I
have said many times, these are the basics that a person should have. So in
any situation, we give one candidate two as a base. That is the body.
To get back to normal, the
paper was originally designed to be eaten, so you must first eat a normal diet.
If you try this,
then you should wear a mask. Even if it's not 14, it's close to a can. If it's not a pepper, it's not a phone, but you
eat a lot of meat and a lot of internal
organs, and you eat everything from head to toe. No, you don't eat. Next, since you really ate a lot, you should eat a little meat. Oh, I get full even if I eat a little. People like this love this guy. I gave him a big ball. Many mad cow disease. Ah, 1. Seodongyo. There are a lot of fluorine isotopes that are
accumulated in human cartilage.
I ate more grains than before. I
ate an absurd amount of meat.
So, after watching Defense Tower, it
seems like I'm halfway through college.
No, the good thing is that the grain evaluation is set. I can't eat it.
This is our intention. Rather, I think I'll eat the cooked mask. Should I
look at it with that thought?
Uh, this is now Anyang liver. There's something like that inside.
Cell. Ah, the period of creation and the smell isn't that strong, but
they cook it. I think they did everything according to Lee Kyung-heon. It's
annoying, so I just eat it, but when I
eat it, it's soft and there are almost no knots, right?
Uh,
um.  Even if you want to do it with your body, how can you crush it with a button?
But now, if you cook it, the flavor gets stronger, and it's even
weirder and more evil. I
cut it little by little and chew it to start with, and I received it from those who swallow it whole.
But now, anyway, if you do it like this and use a note watch, you can experience various
recipes. You can also chop the scrambled eggs you got from a pair of kinds and
put them in with eggplant, or you can eat a hamburger and
stuff it with something like a taffy. There are
parties, right? Photo 6. It's a song, so if you eat it like this, you can feel the Gamma 1 design and add the river naturally. It's all mud-like. If you put a map that's a little sad, it won't show, and if you put in something like interplanetary pressure, why is it like
this? If you come like this, it won't show either, and it's good. If you
protect it like this and listen to the amount of C in the test, this
will set in and the
taste will get used to it. I think that the taste gets used to it after that. It's not that the taste gets better, but you
understand what the taste of liver is.
4.  So now, it's like
this and that, and it's like this. It's like this. There
are so many methods. It's an era where each
art is made and used. Traditionally, no one would dislike red bean.
Or, wear it, water,
something like that. Now, bury the liver, and use this base. And that too,
grind it and don't use it.
There's not a single person in the world who dislikes that. It's
like a Ferrari.
Then, as a candidate, if you
live like this,
yes, of course, it would be good to explain it like this, but while explaining like this, I
just mentioned it once. If you want to do what you want, you
'll catch one person who has a shoulder for about 40 minutes. If you look at it like that, it
's okay. No, but you can use it to some extent. If you
often eat and drink water, don't take a stethoscope separately, then you
don't have to worry about iodine. You
shouldn't have been so stubborn. I think you requested it at a frequent eating speed. Even
though it's a university hospital, if I want to test the language a little, yes. Even
if society says that the patient wants to do it, they say they've moved. It's a
really absurd situation. Even if the patient says they want to do this and that test, they say they've
moved. They say they don't need to. The
cars are
like snakes.  I don't know if it's true or not, but there were a lot of people who said, "
Oh, here, there was a nuance that I was belittling the entire medical community. That's
absolutely not the case.
How can I cut this fat?" Ah, but back in the old days,
after eating something like "i" and "i" and learning insufficiently, I stopped studying and
just stubbornly continued to treat patients with only their own chestnuts.
There are quite a few of these people, more than you'd think. They
went 5 meters.
I remember one time when diversity was a male aspect.
Oh, I think you said that diversity is a male aspect. If it
happens, the name and
such will be 3. Next, the
next hormone is Tame. I
saw it well, but I paid the price just now. It's
not good for me. In that department, they
told people to eat a lot of sugar, and they said, "
Oh, don't eat fat." They said, "If you don't eat fat, what can you eat?" They were eating sugar.
Of course, if you don't eat fat, your body
won't be able to feel it, so thank you. I'm going to make an uploader
in the National Assembly. Sandy is really short. People
usually eat a lot of sugar and sugar.  If you look at it as if it's saturated fat, there's that saturated fat, so
if you eat it like that all the time, you're likely to get cavities. That's why you're a
cavity specialist, right? Oh, don't you know?
That Western Plus doctorate is valuable, because you've studied a lot.
Anyway,
to heal cavities without getting a touch of Hosea, you need fat-soluble vitamins,
ADK, calcium, and minerals like Lang Ying. You
need protein collagen, but you're told not to eat certain things. You're told not to eat meat,
not to eat housework, and don't be afraid of fat, fat-soluble vitamins, vitamin A and D.
All animals have a purpose, so of course
people will go and rot. So now that I have to
come out and do all the work, I'm bringing a fountain and
living, and I've
never done anything else. I've
done land measures and things like that.
If you saw it on TV a while ago that I was going to look into it, you said you packed it all up and
went. My
shoulder hurt, my insurance was overflowing, and
Park Bom was overflowing. My headache was so bad that I couldn't eat it.  It's almost over.
Ah, you can do things like this. Then that money...
Ah,
that detox juice. Fortunately, if your body is healthy and you have
good immunity, you can
bundle it up and say, "Oh, this is obviously good for your body," and then eat and eat again.
How come there are people who are this fat?
Or if the search is too bad, and the virtue is not bad,
then there is nothing to worry about. Then, there is nothing. It wo
n't be like that.
Um, 5.
Hyo-seong Investigation. So, in Barcelona, ​​a long time ago, there was a
man in his 50s with diabetes. He
was so plump and full. If you are not feeling well, what
should you eat? You should eat it to make you feel better. The
ground goes in and it says "Sorel soup." It looks a bit like TOEFL. There is a
lot, but I ordered a latch. I
put more beef and a bowl. Yes, so I ate it.
Asians died later. Jo Sang-yeon. If you
eat a lot of heavy snow for 4 years due to excessive consumption, you will die.
Each person can make it quickly, but
once you have diabetes and Oh Min-hee is not good, it is normal
for an average person to have a festival and taste it to the
extent of the
land.
Uh, something like this.  If you like it, someone might watch this kind of broadcast and
buy a lot of spinach and stuff, and if you
find out, you can see it. There's
no fried food. The
stock price dies right away, and this kind of thing is true that there aren't many cases like that,
but there are
possibilities and cases of fate.
Selenium Midang Aya should take it as a supplement. Why? Selenium is the most abundant zinc in the world. Let's see the tone. Student organic. Give it to the draw. Lamb Selenium M is especially
abundant in the kidneys and the heart. Selenium is also too much for kidney cancer. Selenium is
not good to eat too much.
It's too much. If you eat 300g a day, it
's about Excelen.
So, this short kidney is only eating 300g a day. There
won't be any Tami, but
Helen's point is that it contains a lot of iron. Iron, especially liver, is just the
main part of the song. If you
eat a lot of meat, you don't have to worry about iron, so selenium salt art.
Eat double eyelids.
Oh, read Crystal's
ice bar 3.
What is it? Whether it's
blocking it or not, it's the same. Don't lie and eat the world crab for 8 days.  You can do it
for a few days, it's really itchy and really painful, and your bones are falling off, so if you
follow it, it's
spam 3
tracking. It's gotten better. Leading like this, in the brain, the face, this face, this face,
there's a lot of blood flow, so it comes out a lot from the eyes and things like that. When I wake up, a
lot of water comes out of the cup. When I wake up, while I was sleeping, 2. Who wore clothes for
1 year? Krista 2. What is it? There's a lot of eye boogers
the size of fingernails. How many of them are there? 5. I was like that too. I really had a hard time when I borrowed a large amount of salt. Sit alone with red spots. When I go to the tea house, I laugh and want to eat herbal medicine. If so, I made it. It was a lot of flounder and cockle. It was a
music stand. It was made more.
8. It means like this.
Grilled fish and nose. Imported livestock products. It's a choice. Right? 1. You have to choose.
This
partner. Give it to me. But homosexuality is eating it. It's a harpoon. Give it to me. It's a
dream. It's painful. You can't eat it.
It seems like it'll pop out like this. The fish itself. This guy won't be able to calculate the price. The
app bot. There probably won't be many cases like that, but anyway, that report.  The bitter oil
must have been a shark in Busan.
Hyung, history is average, but I ate something a little seasoned. It's good. It
's not easy to have a company dinner.
If there's beer in the West Sea, you guys ate a lot if there was something delicious.
What the heck is this? What the heck? I remember fried and grilled fish, and it's like getting rid of it. The
beer machine is like a greeting. I do
n't know the liquid crystal, so it's better than the yellow one.
So, is the beer you're talking about here Cass?
4. The minimum is how many handfuls did you eat?
Um, I think so. 100 tons of rice would have been enough, so I drank a little. Rather than
eating, I asked,
so what happened? There
might be cells. I
originally liked trees, but I
love them so much. In the summer, Samcheok 30 l Wang Sa
Ah,
opener Siko, dizzy and comfortable. First, I
have to see my older sister first.
4. Still, in a way, it's a difficult time. It's there,
but rather, you can feel it in your body and suck it more
quickly.
Those who did something said, "I have to go until I'm very far." Ah,
so I ate a lot in a short period of time. The
advantage is that gold keeps relying on it.  If you eat bad food and your insides are not good for
a long time, this is worse.
In cases where the quest car Chicago
TV has improved, it is often defensive. If you check, you won't get sugar and vegetable oil, right? Even if you take out just these two, you have no choice but to take the bus. First of all, the ability to handle that friend's sexual toggle varies from person to person.
Some people can handle that well, but what kind of
person is usually 4 pak-ta and stuff like that? Just because they say they are vegetarian and have a lot of stimulant oil, chicken, pizza, pasta, etc. There are vegetarian doctors, and I don't eat half of those things. Being a vegetarian means that I will
pay a little attention to my health. If you
start paying a little attention like this, you will have no choice but to stop eating processed foods and do this
near this attribute antagonistic photo. In
general, since it is too much talk, it is trash with nowhere else to go, so if you
just do something, your health will
improve a little more than half.
So now, among them, those who started with saliva and water-based toxins are right away.
There will be problems, but if there are problems, they won't be
addressed right away, so it won't come out as a case of having a company dinner and getting better. The
people in the circuit are still people who do it because they only do it on the day, and
Dongcheon 0a Village is
also like this, all aroma directors go around, and there are some like lavender oil, and
there are specific information,
and
if you have a lot of fun, you can do it. Even if you watch it, you'll
know each other often.
Oh,
while watching that broadcast, your English skills are a little bit jealous,
right? How to prevent back pain?
When you talk about hair loss,
when did it start to be related?
Hair loss occurs,
hair ends become unhealthy, and you pull them out, and gray hairs become unhealthy. Udo
Kalita eats like this,
so it's basic.
Of course, you can't completely prevent this. Age is
not a certain level, so you can't think of anything that comes to mind. You
can hold a meeting. Paint your toenails,
take music tests as much as
possible, and do intermittent fasting consistently. Oh, this lifestyle is like
that.
There's also toothpaste that you can't see for 8 seconds. In
other words, it's the amount you brush your teeth with only fluoride.
Uh,
strictly speaking,  Speaking of which, you don't have to be vulnerable. Even if you
do it like this, you can just
write the text separately and
there's nothing special about it. Right? Of
course, there are people who have never even imagined it, let alone taken
medicine, at that restaurant. Well, health and toothpaste have nothing to do with anything.
If you want a refreshing feeling that brings you great things,
just dip Soul in salt water at that time and it's over. Or salt is
black money, so do a little bit of that. After that, you
can play Terra vs. and stuff, right? Class 1. This cartoon is
good resistance. Good news.
But you
can turn it all off with corn and Mac. This kind of thing doesn't come out of the mouth anyway,
but from the inside, so why
the audience? There's no problem.
There's a school.
There's a mountain called Mi-geoni, and
it's a face. The machine makes the upper body with the enemy. The industry issued 0.5.
Cancer cells use York. It's appropriate, and the total of the single is weak. Ya
Show 3-dong 5%. I think it's Sikhye, so I wonder if I should listen to it.
Yes, this is longing.  The club recall is called M5 5g C by Lee Sun-hee.
There's no evidence that this water is bad for the body.
Yes, there are cancer cells, but we have embryonic stem
cells. The person who suffered is large, and there's no way our embryonic stem cells exist.
There's no research on this in our bodies, no matter how much it's actually like this. The
pen scanner box is
n't urgently needed by the investigation department. Those doctors
just don't need to take responsibility for it because of its size. But if you leave out the T story, it's
just people. Regardless, they're
examples of
people who like to do business with people for a long time. There's no evidence. Rather, if you're going to talk about the inside of the blood, there
needs to be some evidence, right? There's something.
But no matter how much it causes it in people, there's
no regulation.
Our big cells are like this. The
stem cells are cancer cells, so that's why. Hey,
I don't know what you're talking about. They say it tastes good. It
's 9:30, so
Inseo Bansaeng, the
abacus problem is higher than the upper limit. I've seen it here before, so it's
amazing.
I'm coming to see it right away. The floating turret is yours.
At the end of the
story, whenever I hear you say that, I go in and say, "Do something good for your body on purpose.
" If the
bad thing is good, return the value. If it doesn't get better, suck it up.
I'm a healthy person.
Most people don't speak English. So, I
took a selfie. I made a video using a dot room and made a video using a dot room. I
didn't have any information in the first place. Most of them don't speak English. There
's no research. There's no research. There's no research. The research we're talking about here is 0
people. There's no experiment. They
just don't wear it and do
epidemiological surveys and observational studies. They
do meaningless things and eat everything.
Well,
there are a lot of bad leaders. There are
bad bad people.
It's because it's 50,000. No, you have to
see it as a combination. Even if it's not
of, I use a clear and natural toothpaste.
Even an idiot who doesn't eat or drink from the water doesn't have tartar. Make sure to
take care of your vitamin K. Do you have
calcium? If something strange happens, it'll disappear, so
don't worry about it. If so, you can find 5r in a short period of time.  What, you don't even drink tea like this?
Haven't you seen anything else like that?
I think everyone has probably experienced it at least once, knowingly or unknowingly. In our country, especially, no matter how much you
understand and say you
hate grass, there are times when you force yourself to eat it while hoping for it, and
in our country, the drinking water system
eats others and beans, and things like that a lot.
Ah, now, after 3 or 4 years, a lot of houses have been stolen, and cancer, especially
with merit, beans, let's use it,
and there must have been a lot of rioters. Since childhood, there
must be no 3 groups that don't eat it well.
So, if you quit, you
can't help but experience symptoms like 7, even if it's just a light 2,
8, 4, and more, and constipation, and you have to go back and forth, and you have to
wake up every night to go to the bathroom, and
in fact, when you go, it's so urgent and you have to go without meaning to, and you have to do it in a way, and it's really
hard to go like this.
Yes, I understood the
pork last time, and the more I looked at it, then it's better than raw pork belly. 10. 1.2
Section 3 This is as expensive as I am.
Oh, but Section 10, I bought pork belly.  I see you
bought the 2-course history and salted it yourself. If
I had to
go to the organic store right now and eat it, I would have to make a choice, but
I'm going to buy 10 pounds and cook it at home. I'll
buy Oki in advance and dissolve salt in it. Are you
afraid of third-party companies? Of course, it's not that the commercially available Acorn or something like that is terribly
bad,
but that's better.
Of course, 2% salt is better, but in fact, it's difficult to compare them one-on-one. Uh,
compared to regular bacon, it's very expensive. You use 15% shipping. It
stops at G. It can't be C-grade,
so that's why it's a little bit.
Uh, sodium nitrite isn't bad. It's
absurd. I
'll go later. Sodium nitrite itself is very traditional and has been used since ancient times. It's
not something that's been created recently, so the
rich only need the minimum amount. It's
not automatically bad or anything. That's
your advantage. You can't say that you
missed out on something like Teller Matthews or used it negligently.  The things that can't be done with the sun
are the ones that
don't add sodium, which is the nitrite component that's extracted from the celery.
Sodium nitrite is not in celery, but
we can't control how much is in celery. So, if you usually put celery juice like that,
you can know, but the actual amount is much more than what you calculated, up to 50 times more.
Okay, eat it.
Just bring in a
ticket. Oh, you know that?
Take it. Also, like this, thoroughly eat food and well.
If you age meat for a long time, enzymes are sent to the body, so it's
small.
When you have an upset stomach, when you have difficulty digesting, when you're not feeling well, it's a shame to eat these things. It's a
shame to absorb them, so it's better
not to buy them.
It's true that smart celery can still do the wind,
or really, Ah, Jun-ah, it's concentrated and you have to drink it.
So, generally, when we use it, it's very shameful, so it's used to a very small
amount of sodium, and it's
been used traditionally,
so it's not really that much.  It's not something to worry about.
What's worse, eating it now or not? It's better to eat it.
So, when you make something like this taker, if you make it at home by pasting the filling yourself,
how do you sleep without that?
Of course, when you make it, there are people everywhere, but since the
game sees a lot of meat to send animals, I don't think that's the case in advance.
Um, you
don't have to contact me like this.
Hey, but let's put a lot of other things in the hand notebook. I don't have a storage frame yet.
Um,
salt, sodium, these two are making it. How much is it?
Other things like this? Even women go in, right? I've
heard the vocabulary in the problem once.
0 When finishing it. The
front leaf is also included. Don't use it often and
really send it.
In addition to the evil outpost, what if the sun sets?